import { FlashcardType } from './types';

const flashcards: FlashcardType[] = [
    { id: 1, question: "hello", answer: "olá" },
    { id: 2, question: "goodbye", answer: "adeus" },
    { id: 3, question: "apple", answer: "maçã" },
    { id: 4, question: "banana", answer: "banana" },
    { id: 5, question: "house", answer: "casa" },
    { id: 6, question: "dog", answer: "cachorro" },
    { id: 7, question: "cat", answer: "gato" },
    { id: 8, question: "book", answer: "livro" },
    { id: 9, question: "car", answer: "carro" },
    { id: 10, question: "tree", answer: "árvore" },
    { id: 11, question: "sun", answer: "sol" },
    { id: 12, question: "moon", answer: "lua" },
    { id: 13, question: "water", answer: "água" },
    { id: 14, question: "fire", answer: "fogo" },
    { id: 15, question: "earth", answer: "terra" },
    { id: 16, question: "air", answer: "ar" },
    { id: 17, question: "school", answer: "escola" },
    { id: 18, question: "student", answer: "aluno" },
    { id: 19, question: "teacher", answer: "professor" },
    { id: 20, question: "computer", answer: "computador" },
    { id: 21, question: "phone", answer: "telefone" },
    { id: 22, question: "music", answer: "música" },
    { id: 23, question: "movie", answer: "filme" },
    { id: 24, question: "friend", answer: "amigo" },
    { id: 25, question: "family", answer: "família" },
    { id: 26, question: "love", answer: "amor" },
    { id: 27, question: "happiness", answer: "felicidade" },
    { id: 28, question: "sadness", answer: "tristeza" },
    { id: 29, question: "anger", answer: "raiva" },
    { id: 30, question: "peace", answer: "paz" },
    { id: 31, question: "war", answer: "guerra" },
    { id: 32, question: "work", answer: "trabalho" },
    { id: 33, question: "play", answer: "jogar" },
    { id: 34, question: "eat", answer: "comer" },
    { id: 35, question: "drink", answer: "beber" },
    { id: 36, question: "sleep", answer: "dormir" },
    { id: 37, question: "dream", answer: "sonhar" },
    { id: 38, question: "smile", answer: "sorrir" },
    { id: 39, question: "laugh", answer: "rir" },
    { id: 40, question: "cry", answer: "chorar" },
    { id: 41, question: "run", answer: "correr" },
    { id: 42, question: "walk", answer: "andar" },
    { id: 43, question: "swim", answer: "nadar" },
    { id: 44, question: "jump", answer: "pular" },
    { id: 45, question: "fly", answer: "voar" },
    { id: 46, question: "drive", answer: "dirigir" },
    { id: 47, question: "travel", answer: "viajar" },
    { id: 48, question: "read", answer: "ler" },
    { id: 49, question: "write", answer: "escrever" },
    { id: 50, question: "listen", answer: "ouvir" },
    { id: 51, question: "speak", answer: "falar" }
];

export default flashcards;